price2spy.com 2019-07-17

# Privacy / refund policy - Price2Spy® - Competitor price monitoring

This privacy policy sets out how Price2Spy uses and protects any information that you give us when you use our service. 

First of all, we understand how sensitive and discrete are the information you have in your Price2Spy account. You can rest assured that we are committed to ensuring that the privacy of your data is fully protected, both in sense of technical data security as well as in business sense. 

### What We Collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name

  * contact information including email address

  * demographic information such as country location
  * information related to competitors you want monitored
  * information related to products you want monitored

### What We Do With the Information We Gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.

  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
  * After you subscribe for Price2Spy service, we may publish your company logo on our Website, as a sign that you're a client of ours (absolutely no other information regarding your Price2Spy account will ever be disclosed!). However, if you do not like the idea of your logo being displayed on Price2Spy pages, do let us know, and your logo will be removed.

### Data Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

Since customers‘ data privacy is one of our main priorities, we enable you to fully control your personal data online under the law regulation on data privacy and protection by General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). 

We as a company have been GDPR compliant and fully respect the legislation. 

### Sharing Your Personal Information

We will only share personal data with others when we are legally permitted to do so. 

We may share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights. 

We may also use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.You can opt out of targeted advertising by: [myaccount.google.com/privacy](https://myaccount.google.com/privacy)

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below. 

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. 

When you place an order through the site, we will maintain your order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information. 

### How We Use Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

### Links to Other Websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

### Refund Policy

Since Price2Spy offers 30-day trial, we assume you have enough time test it's features and see their benefits to your business. 

Therefore, we will accept refund requests only if it appears that Price2Spy cannot any longer monitor the sites it was able to monitor in your trial period. 

Refund requests must be made up to 30 days after the payment. 

### Changes to Our Privacy Statement

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. This privacy statement was last updated on 24/05/2018. 

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at info@price2spy.com or by mail using the details provided below: WEBCentric d.o.o. Ulofa Palmea 6b 11160 Beograd SERBIA
